I have to do this, this advocacy and educating people that I do.
Voting.
Yeah.
The reason why is that it is attached to, it has tentacles to so many other things, right?
So voting, just as an act, can shift the way that money is spent for police, right?
Right. Voting as an act can shift the way school boards are, you know, dealing with our children.
Right. Voting as an act can change the way that our bodies are the way that we're allowed to handle our bodies.
Right. Now, some people are like, well, I think that is overly simplistic.
I think that voting is obviously corrupt. And I think that we are in a country where we over popularize this idea that voting has an effect on things.
And what I'll say to that is the act of us voting together then also breeds community.
Yeah.
Community breeds power.
And power can shift.
Yeah.
Right. So it's not as basic as just the idea of like, oh, I just wish y'all would go and vote for the president.
That's not it. It's, it's, it's like Mr. Miyagi. It's like a wax on, wax off.
Like voting is the practice.
It's the wax on, wax off. It's not the crane kick.
You know, the crane kick is when we learn how to utilize what it took for us to even get there to vote in a, in a real actualized way.
When we start using community to shift things through force, through finance, right?
Through shit, through fury.
Um, and so why, so the reason why I'm like, so, uh, adamant about voting has a number of different tiers to it.
And I think it's on a basic, basic, basic level.
It's just like, if you are not engaged in the system that is controlling you, controlling, yeah, you're right.
Then how do you shift that system?
Yeah.
Are you okay with this?
And that's the thing I see.
I feel like a lot of people are not okay with this, but they're not sure in what ways to change it.
And too many people's way of doing things is I'm just going to disengage.
We have an avoidant society.
They have successfully created an entire nation of people who have avoidant, avoidant attachment syndrome.
Yeah.
No, that's facts.
I do think there's a lot of, I think there's like, I think there's a few different levels of the apathy towards voting, right?